A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
The Library of Virginia
43861, 44223, 44409, 44396, 44409, 44568, 44640, 44847, 45144, 45238, 45268, 51080, 51901, 51962, 52645
90 cu. ft. (90 boxes)
Virginia Housing Development Authority
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, Virginia and accessioned: Accession 43861, 10 July 20008; Accession 44223, transferred 15 April 2009; Accession 44396, transferred 25 June 2009; Accession 44409, transferred 22 July 2009; Accession 44568, transferred 19 Oct 2009; Accession 44847, 3 March 2010; Accession 45238, 7 October 2010; Accession 45268, 1 December 2010; Accession 51080, transferred 6 Nov 2013; Accession 51901, 29 August 2016; Accession 51962, 1 February 2017; Accession 52645, 3 March 2019.
Biographical Information
The Virginia Housing Development Authority (VHDA) is the state's mortgage finance agency. Created in 1972 by the Virginia General Assembly, its mission is to help Virginians with low and moderate income levels attain quality, affordable housing whether through rental programs or home ownership. VHDA strives to overcome barriers to homeownership, as well as to offer easily accessible products, programs and services. VHDA has developed several loan programs designed to meet the needs of low-and moderate-income consumers.
The Virginia Housing Development Authority is self-supporting and does not use tax dollars to fund its lending programs. The Authority sells bonds to the private sector in order to support its lending programs. From its own operating funds, VHDA finances the Virginia Housing Fund, which makes loans to homeownership and rental programs that serve Virginians who cannot be served by its traditional bond-funded programs.
The Virginia Housing Development Authority is a quasi-government agency, and as such, is subject to certain supervisory powers of the governor and the General Assembly. VHDA is required to submit annual reports of its operating and financial status, which are subject to review by the Auditor of Public Accounts. VHDA’s Board of Commissioners is composed of 11 members, all of whom are appointed by the governor. Eight members are direct appointees, including a Housing Choice Voucher Program representative. Day-to-day management is left to the executive director. In 1999, Susan F. Dewey became the executive director of VHDA.
Scope and Content
Director's correspondence and subject files document the planning, direction, and implementation of agency programs and are evidence of actions and policy decisions. Include correspondence, board meeting materials, memoranda, reports, subject files, financial records, and legislative files.
This collection consists of multiple accessions, so please note both accession number and box number when requesting records.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records
Contents List
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 43861), 1975-1981., Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes).
  Arranged in original order.
  - Executive Director: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1979 Feb-Apr (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1979 May-July (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1979 Aug-Oct (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1979 Nov-Dec (Box 1)
  - Housing and Community Development Board meeting, 1979 Apr 16 (Box 1)
  - Housing and Community Development Board meeting, 1979 July 16 (Box 1)
  - Housing and Community Development Board meeting, 1979 Aug 20 (Box 1)
  - Housing and Community Development Board meeting, 1979 Sept 17 (Box 1)
  - Housing and Community Development Board meeting, 1979 Nov 19 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Jan 16 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Feb 20 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Mar 20 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Apr 17 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 May 15 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 June 19 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 July 17 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Aug 21 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Sept 18 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Oct 18 (Box 2)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Nov 20 (Box 3)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1979 Dec 18 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director: Memoranda, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Annual Housing Study Commission workshop, 1979 (Box 3)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Jan 17 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Feb 21 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Mar 21 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Apr 18 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 May 16 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 June 20 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 July 18 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Aug 24 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Sept 19 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Oct 17 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Nov 21 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1978 Dec 19 (Box 4)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Correspondence, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Section 8 correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Section 8 Set-Aside Allocation Funds, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Flexible Subsidy meeting, 1980 Feb 5 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Neighborhood Strategy Area Program, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Title I, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Richmond Area Office, 1977-1980 (Box 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Washington Area Office, 1977-1980 (Box 5)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Dec 21 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Nov 16 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Oct 19 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Sept 21 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Aug 17 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 July 20 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 June 15 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 May 18 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Apr 20 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Mar 16 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Feb 17 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1976 Jan 20 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1975 Dec 16 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1975 Nov 18 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1975 Oct 21 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1975 Sept 16 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1975 Aug 19 (Box 6)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1975 July 15 (Box 6)
- Board meeting records (Accession 43937), 1977., Extent: 1 cu. ft. (1 box).
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 May 17 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 June 21 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 July 19 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 Aug 16 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting (Special), 1977 Sept 9 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 Sept 20 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 Oct 18 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 Nov 15 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Board meeting, 1977 Dec 20 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 43938), 1974-1984., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1978 Jan-Feb (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1978 Mar-Apr (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1978 May-June (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1978 July-Aug (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Corresondence, 1978 Sept-Oct (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Correspondence, 1978 Nov-Dec (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Memoranda, 1978 Mar (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Memoranda, 1978 Apr (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Memoranda, 1978 May-June (Box 1)
  - Executive Director: Outgoing correspondence, 1977 Jan-Mar (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Executive Memoranda, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Executive Director: Intra-Office Memoranda, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Development, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1976 Sept-Dec (Box 2)
  - Volunteers, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Office of Commerce and Resources, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Robb Administration, 1978-1982 (Box 2)
  - Legislators, State, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Legislators, U.S., 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Single Family correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Board of Commissioners, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1982 Jul-Sept (Box 2)
  - Legislators, State, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Legislators, U.S., 1984 (Box 3)
  - Administration Director, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Personnel Director, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Computer Operations, 1984 (Box 3)
  - public Information, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Articles of interest, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Support Services, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Commissioners, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Commissioners, Dinner for, 1984 June (Box 3)
  - The Hopkins Commission, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency Head Retreat, 1984 May (Box 3)
  - Commissioners Retreat, 1984 Oct (Box 3)
  - Internal Auditor, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Finance Director, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Director, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Director - Complaints, 1984 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 44223), 1976-1995., Extent: 5 cu. ft. (5 boxes).
  - Commissioners, 1976-1978 (Box 1)
  - Section 8, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Burstein memos, undated (Box 1)
  - Recruitment, undated (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, 1978 (Box 1)
  - EEO, 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Office of Minority Business Enterprise, 1977-1980 (Box 1)
  - HOME, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Indian Reservation Lands, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Handicapped, 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - Shockoe Slip Association, 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - NLHA, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Lamar Society, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Ullman bill - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 2)
  - Duncan bill - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 2)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Management Committee notes and agendas, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Legal Director, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Christian Barton, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Social Security Withdrawal, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Director, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Complaints, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: ARC, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: Target areas, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Director, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Mortgage Revenue Bond Briefing Books, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Homebuilder's Breakfast, 1984 (Box 4)
  - VHDA Newsletters and Annual Reports, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Calendars (John Ritchie), 1990 July-1991 Jan (Box 5)
  - Calendars (John Ritchie), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Calendars (John Ritchie), 1992 July-Dec (Box 5)
  - Calendars (John Ritchie), 1991 Feb-Dec (Box 5)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 44396), 1972-2007., Extent: 12 cu. ft. (12 boxes).
  - VHDA Annual Reports, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
  - Articles of interest, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
  - Audits, 1978-1982 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 2)
  - Budget, 1981 FY (Box 2)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
  - Meetings and speaking engagements (John Ritchie), 1980-1982 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Urban Developments (HUD), 1982 (Box 4)
  - Federal Housing Administration (FHA), 1972-1982 (Box 4)
  - Management memos, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Administration, 1980-1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - EEO, 1972-1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Emergency evacuation, 1972-1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Resignation, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Information Office, 1972-1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Personnel, 1980-1982 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Personnel - Political activity, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Personnel - Salary Survey, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Interoffice memos - Personnel - Attitude Survey, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Coopertives, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
  - Budget working papers, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Budget revisions (John Ritchie), 1980 FY (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Goals for VHDA, 1977-1979 (Box 6)
  - Deferred Compensation Plan, 1980 (Box 6)
  - VHDA visitors, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Investment and Guidelines information, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Investment Banker Guidelines, undated (Box 6)
  - Cost Certification Reviews, 1981 (Box 6)
  - PMM - Operations System Study, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - PMM Report - Review of Personnel Function, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Conventional Multifamily Loan Program, 1978-1982 (Box 6)
  - Single Family Loan Program, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Single Family Policy Statement, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Appalachian Housing Fund, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Demonstration Home, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - One person household regulation, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Senate / House Energy Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Energy Conservation and Rehabilitation Loan Program, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Section 8 Single Family Bond Program, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Section 8 Fair Market Rents, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Section 8 Existing, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Multifamily Conventional Loan Program, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
  - Rehabilitation Loan Program, 1978-1982 (Box 7)
  - Section 8 Mod Rehab, 1979-1982 (Box 7)
  - UP and I, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
  - Mini-Computer acquisition, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Computer, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Beach Rehab Loan Program, 1979-1982 (Box 7)
  - New ideas, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
  - Rehab Tax Exemption, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Competitive Bid Sale, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Program ideas, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Management Program, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Aggie Bonds, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
  - Alternative Financing of Section 8 Housing, 1978 (Box 7)
  - New Programs - GEMS, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Proposed New Programs - Block Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
  - Proposed New Programs - Condo Conversion Policy, 1979-1982 (Box 7)
  - Clinchport Relocation, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Weatherization Program, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Proposed New Program - Housing for Handicapped, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
  - Mobile Homes, 1980 (Box 7)
  - ,Navy Housing 1981 (Box 7)
  - Post-Construction Evaluation Program, 1977 (Box 7)
  - President's Reorganization Project, 1977 (Box 7)
  - R/E Syndication and seminars, 1977 (Box 7)
  - New Rental Housing Program, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Tax Increment Financing, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Welfare Reform - Subsidized Housing, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services: Division Director, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services: Personnel, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services: Performance Appraisal System, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services: Public Relations, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services: Annual Report, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services: Newsletter, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services: Support Services, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: Division Director, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: Commissioners, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: State Legislators, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: Speaking Engagements, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: VAPDC, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: Institute of Government (UVA), 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: Charlottesville Housing Forum, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: GE Housing Industry Conference, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: NLHA, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: Internal Auditor, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Executive: United Way Campaign, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Finance: Division Director, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Housing Management: Division Director, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management: Complaints, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management: Mod Rehab, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management: Hubert Young, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management: Section 8 Existing, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management: Section 8 New, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Legal: Division Director, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Multi-Family: Division Director, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Multi-Family: Complaints, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Multi-Family: Mortgage Loan Committee, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Planning and Research: Division Director, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Planning and Research: ARC, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Planning and Research: Rental Rehab, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Single Family: Division Director, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Single Family: Complaints, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Single Family: Servicing, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: Administration and Finance, Secretary of, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: Attorney General, 1983 Jan-July (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: Douthat Workshop, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: Governor's Office, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: Miscellaneous State Agencies, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: General Assembly, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: Legislative Services, Division of, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia: HUD - Central, D.C., Region III, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Expense Reports, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Expense Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Expense Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Expense Reports, 1992-1999 (Box 12)
  - Expense Reports, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Management Committee Notes and Agendas, 1992-1996 (Box 12)
  - Management Committee Notes and Agendas, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Management Committee Notes and Agendas, 2007 (Box 12)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 44409), 1983-1987., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - General Assembly - Chicago Bond Financing, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Set asides, 1979 FY (Box 2)
  - Computer installation, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Programs and production, 1979 FY (Box 2)
  - General Assembly, 1980 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly - Legislative Coordinator, 1979 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly - Industry Development Authority, 1979 (Box 2)
  - General Assembly - Administrative Procedures Act Amendment, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Credit Facility Agreement, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Budget Revision, 1979 FY (Box 2)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Washington Liaison Office, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous State Agencies, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Legislative Services, Division of, 1984 (Box 2)
  - JLARC, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Monitor Long-Term Care, 1984 (Box 2)
  - CARE, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1984 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Urban Developmnet (HUD) - DC Area Office, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - Region III, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - Richmond Area Office, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Houisng Innovations, 1984 (Box 2)
  - NAHRO, NLHA, 1984 (Box 2)
  - VAHCDL, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Administration and Finance, Secretary of, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Resources, Secretary of, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Office, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - General correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous state agencies, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation Interagency Planning Council, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation research project, 1985 (Box 3)
  - General Assembly, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Farmer's Home Administration, 1985 (Box 3)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office - Multifamily Housing Study, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - Central Office, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - D.C. Area Office, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - Richmond Area Office, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - Region III, Philadelphia, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Federal FY 1986 Budget, 1985 (Box 3)
  - U.S. Government - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Director - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Director - Facilities Study, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Director -VHDA Annex Building, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Director - Office space arrangement, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Director - Manpower planning analysis, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Computer Operations - EDP Steering Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Personnel - Telephone techniques, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Personnel - Training and Development, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Public Information - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Public Information - Good News, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Services: Support Services, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Finance Division: Bond Call 82A, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Finance Division: Bond call 81A and 82A, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Finance Division: Comparisons and other financials, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management Division: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management Division: Mod Rehabilitation, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management Division: Project Account Amendment, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Legal Division: General Counsel, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management Division: Barton, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Committe of Navy Housing, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Ad Hoc Committee on Navy Housing, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Elderly Housing Proposals, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Multifamily Division: Multifamily Loan Program, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: ARC, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: New Programs, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rural Homesteading, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Contingent Commitment Program, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Policy Statement, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Recycling Single Family Funds, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Administative Services: Director, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Budget, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Computer Operations, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Personnel, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: CMP Study, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Staff Development Report, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Training and Development, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Public Relations, 1984-1985 (Box 5)